[Fangs of Fortune]
[Episode 28]
Princess Longyu has a bad temper
and hates to see people,
especially men.
So, we had to let Zhuo and the others
stay in the White Emperor Tower.
Am I not a man?
You're an ape.
Whenever you need me,
I'll come to your aid.
Well,
I wanted to eavesdrop on Princess Longyu,
so I cast a spell on Mr. Zhuo and the others
to carry voices
to their ears.
But now,
they heard our words of love.
It's embarrassing.
Shame on you, Zhao Yuanzhou.
Bastard!
He's talking nonsense!
Huh.
Mr. Zhuo,
after you became a demon,
your voice turned more sonorous when cursing.
But you'd better be careful.
It seems
your ice marks
are about to crack.
If Jiu were here
and saw the powerful great demon
Mr. Zhuo has become,
he'd scream with delight.
Jiu is most afraid of great demons.
I think he'd scream
with terror.
What are we having for dinner?
Sweet and sour ribs?
What do you mean?
Then why didn't you
buy sugar and ribs?
What?
The ingredients are hard to get in the Wilderness.
I'll make it when we return to the mortal world.
She's coming.
Baize Goddess.
Are you Zhu Yan?
See?
I told you
everyone in the Wilderness knows me.
The notorious Zhu Yan.
Next time, please finish your words in one go.
Baize Goddess, why did you free me
and summon me here?
I want
to ask you for a dragon scale.
Interesting.
Why are there so many people who want my dragon scale today?
Someone else asked you for your dragon scale, too?
If you don't want to die,
give me your dragon scale.
A dragon has a reverse scale,
which you can't touch.
If you touch it, the dragon will get angry.
Neither can you snatch the scale.
If you do, its spiritual energy will disappear.
Only if the dragon gives you the scale willingly
can it resurrect everything.
You don't even know that?
Oh.
There's someone else.
Princess Longyu.
Your old friend
asked me to send you a letter.
[Meng Xuan]
Meng Xuan.
[To Long Yu] [Meng Xuan]
[Meng Xuan]
There's nothing to expect of this love.
Although I regret it, it's too late.
Meng Xuan.
Where did you get this?
You want to know?
Give me Zhu Yan's inner core, and I'll tell you.
Why do you want the dragon scale?
I'm poisoned.
I want to detoxify.
Poisoned?
The goddess is really good at making up stories.
Besides books about demons, there must also be many novels
in the Archives.
She must have read a lot.
Novels?
When I was young,
my grandfather didn't allow me to read novels,
calling them a breach of morality.
I don't quite understand that.
The novels Wen Xiao read
are not the same
as the novels your grandfather mentioned.
I want the dragon scale
just to live
so that I can stay with him
forever.
Am I right?
Of course.
They say
people who love each other don't always
get together and live happily ever after.
They don't know
there are faithful lovers
who are willing to give up everything for each other.
That's us.
Faithful lovers?
When a human and a demon fall in love with each other,
it's destined to be a tragedy.
You owe me the dragon scale.
You owe me a life.
Have you forgotten?
No, I haven't.
I'm willing to hold your hands
and spend the rest of my life with you.
Meng Xuan.
These are the Feng Pearl and the Huang Pearl,
secret treasures of the Longyu Clan.
Now,
I'm giving the Feng Pearl to you.
Feng and Huang are two birds that are always together.
If you don't deceive me,
I'll be with you in life and in death.
Darling.
Don't bother.
I was bitten by the Black Bee.
Herbs in the mortal world
can't cure me.
You will be cured.
I asked Princess Longyu for help.
The reverse scale on the back of her neck can cure all diseases
and bring the dead back to life.
You and the baby
will be fine.
Drink the medicine.
I asked Princess Longyu for help.
The reverse scale on the back of her neck can cure all diseases
and bring the dead back to life.
But he didn't know
every creature in the river
could talk to me.
He lied to me.
He just wanted to save his wife and child.
I hated him.
I was jealous of the woman he had been protecting.
So, I wanted to kill them.
Senior.
Meng Xuan.
Yes.
Well...
Take the medicine
to my home and give it to my wife.
Okay.
I have to go out of town now.
Don't worry.
I'll go now.
Okay.
But I couldn't bear to kill Meng Xuan.
So, I asked him to meet me outside of town
so he wouldn't be home.
Unexpectedly, he didn't come.
Wen He.
Meng.
Where is Wen Xiao?
I haven't seen her for a long time.
She's grown taller, right?
I heard my senior's wife has lost her appetite recently.
I brought her some plums.
Something smells good.
What is it?
Mrs...
Wen,
it has been...
Wen! Wen!
Guards.
Guards!
I secretly put some Bone-Melting Incense,
a unique poison of our clan,
in Meng Xuan's house.
Bone-Melting Incense?
It's a diffusive poison
made from red mermaid pearls.
Anyone who smells it rots and dies immediately.
It's strictly forbidden to take this poison to the mortal world.
I only wanted to kill his wife and child.
I didn't expect Meng Xuan would stand me up
and go home early.
Maybe God thought he was hateful, too.
He deserved it.
Is there a saying
in the mortal world that goes,
"An innocent person's only crime
is to own something valuable"?
Princess Longyu
may never be able to tell
if her admirers
come for her
or for her dragon scale.
People with a treasure
are always surrounded by bad wolves
and cunning foxes.
In most cases,
in order to protect the treasure,
they become a bloodthirsty beast, too.
It's a choice.
She could choose not to.
No matter what,
sharp teeth and claws
can't be used to hurt the innocent and weak.
Meng Xuan was hateful.
But you deserve death, too.
Meng Xuan's wife was pregnant.
How could you do that?
You also killed my father.
I was guided here by the short flute.
I'm glad I found you.
I'll pay you back
what I owe you.
But I have a request.
What is it?
If you want my scale,
give me his inner core.
Wen Xiao.
I thought
I could use Princess Longyu's guilt for me
to make her hand over her dragon scale.
Wen Xiao.
But I didn't expect that...
Don't blame yourself.
Not everyone is as kind as you.
Don't let others' wickedness
change your kindness.
Hey.
Don't you think
you look too grim?
It may make others think the Wilderness is going to collapse again.
The Wilderness is not going to collapse.
You are.
I can't believe you're still joking.
Handing over Zhao Yuanzhou's inner core is not an option.
Let's find another way.
Zhao Yuanzhou.
Why is it not an option?
If you hand over my inner core,
you can get the dragon scale
to repair your Cloud Light Sword.
Zhao Yuanzhou.
What you said
insulted Zhuo.
Zhao Yuanzhou,
keep
your inner core.
I won't exchange it
for anything,
not even the Cloud Light Sword.
It's useless to look at them.
The sword is mine.
I have the final say.
But the inner core is mine.
Zhao Yuanzhou,
don't push me.
I'm not.
I just don't want you
to face this hard choice.
So, I'm going to choose for you.
And it seems
Pei Sijing and Ying Lei
agree with me.
I know you want to save Jiu,
but Zhao Yuanzhou is also our friend.
Can you say
one friend is more important than another?
Why not?
You're a coward,
and you want to treat them fairly,
but that doesn't mean everyone's like you.
If you don't dare to choose,
I dare!
Jiu is more important!
If everyone were fine today,
I wouldn't force Zhao Yuanzhou.
If
Princess Longyu wanted my inner core,
I'd give it to her immediately.
But today,
if either Jiu or Zhao Yuanzhou must die,
I'll choose Zhao Yuanzhou
without hesitation.
Ying Lei.
Every one of you
is saying
pretty words.
Don't you want
to be favored
and be chosen firmly?
Do you think Zhao Yuanzhou doesn't want to be favored
He
has never been chosen firmly.
Oh, that's not true.
He has.
Malicious energy chose him,
and then everyone gave up on him.
Mr. Zhuo,
don't you want to save Jiu?
He's being kept in that dark place.
He must be scared.
Every time he's most scared,
you are the one
he wants to turn to!
Mr. Zhuo,
Jiu needs you.
No matter what,
I'm on Zhuo's side.
We don't agree
to sacrifice Zhao Yuanzhou to get the dragon scale.
It's not "we."
It's only you and Zhuo Yichen.
I thought
we were like-minded.
I was wrong.
Today,
anyone who wants to take Zhao Yuanzhou's inner core
has to defeat me first.
Don't bother.
Don't use violence.
I'll take out my inner core
myself.
Great Demon,
no!
Zhao Yuanzhou!
I brought Zhao Yuanzhou's inner core.
Where is the letter?
[To Long Yu]
This letter doesn't mean anything
to me now.
I knew you were still alive.
That day, I did go to the forest
as I promised.
The man who rotted and died
after smelling your Bone-Melting Incense
was not me
but my junior.
He was the real Meng Xuan.
Now that I think about it,
I did have feelings for you.
My feelings for you saved me
but caused the death of my loved one.
When you tried to get my dragon scale
by deceiving me,
did you ever think there would be karma?
Karma?
God is on my side.
After so many years,
you came to me again.
Since you're here, I want you dead.
I've been planning for so many years,
waiting for this day to come
to avenge my wife
and my unborn child!
[Respected by Generations]
That was Pei Sijing's Shadow Hunting Arrow.
It seems you're cooperating
with the Demon Hunting Bureau.
[There are fish in the water]
[Princess Longyu can communicate with all creatures in the water]
[One-Word Spell: act]
Zhao Yuanzhou.
Why is it not an option?
If you hand over my inner core,
you can get the dragon scale.
Are you sure Princess Longyu is coming?
I left some spies at the Chongwu Camp.
The information should be accurate.
What about you?
Are you sure the fake inner core you gave her
can fool Wen Zongyu?
Wen Zongyu is always sinister and cunning.
I hope his strong desire for my inner core
will make him lower his guard.
It seems we're okay now,
but
I don't think he is.
Leave it to me.
Zhuo.
Go away.
Okay.
If I were Mr. Zhuo,
I would be furious.
Most importantly, Mr. Zhuo
is usually serious.
We all acted dramatically.
Only he showed his true feelings.
It was so embarrassing.
Today,
anyone who wants to take Zhao Yuanzhou's inner core
has to defeat me first.
The thing is, Zhuo was in the wrong position.
If he had seen it,
the fish in the water would have seen it, too.
It has nothing to do with his position.
Mr. Zhuo is upright
and honest.
Usually, when he's asked to lie,
his ears turn extremely red.
If we had made him lie,
the fish in the water would have laughed so hard
that they'd have turned upside-down.
So funny.
She's coming.
I've applied a poison of our clan to the inner core.
You're going to die soon.
Don't you miss your wife and child?
Go to hell and keep them company.
I'm going with you.
So, now you know
[Carry on the Legacy]
why I asked you to meet me here, right?
You gave them your reverse scale?
Yes.
But Wen Xiao doesn't know
that for us of the Longyu Clan, once we hand over our reverse scales,
we die.
Yet you know it.
I loved you
and trusted you,
so I told you all my secrets.
But what about you?
The one who deserves to die is you,
Meng Xuan.
You're still calling me by the wrong name.
Don't you think you're pathetic?
I knew you'd play a trick,
so I got prepared.
You didn't let me down.
[Carry on the Legacy]
Meng Xuan!
I'm not Meng Xuan!
It's you.
You killed my wife
and my unborn child.
It's all you demons' fault.
But don't worry.
I'll make all demons in the Wilderness
die with you.
Shall we let him go?
There are about a dozen demonized humans in the yard.
My One-Word Spells won't work on them.
Your Cloud Light Sword hasn't been repaired.
If we fight with them directly,
we'll be at a disadvantage.
Let's not alert them
and see what Wen Zongyu wants to do.
Miss,
I'm in a rush to see a patient.
Sorry.
I'm Long…
Long Yu.
What's your name?
Meng Xuan.
[The Bloodline is Carried On]
Goddess,
what are you thinking?
I'm thinking about how to repair the Cloud Light Sword
to keep Zhuo alive
and how to defeat Li Lun
to keep Bai Jiu alive.
What about me?
You're not thinking about me?
I'm also thinking about you.
Since I met you, an evil great demon,
I've learned more.
What can you learn from me?
Being pessimistic and world-weary?
People can't choose their origins,
but they can choose their own lives.
♫You wear candlelight like a robe, awaiting dawn♫
You and Li Lun
♫While I cradle heartache, year after year, on and on♫
saw Wen Zongyu kill little demons cruelly with your own eyes.
♫In dreams, my hometown♫
♫Lies under frost♫
Li Lun chose to kill everyone
♫All sounds♫
not from his race.
♫Are lost♫
You, on the contrary,
♫The wind brushes against rivers and hills♫
are willing to believe that people are innately good
and that all living beings
♫Wild blooms refuse to fall♫
deserve to be protected and cherished.
♫They've seen every hue the world has borne♫
Although we have different origins,
♫Which blossom is meant for me?♫
we ended up at the same destination.
♫As songs are sung, how many truly understand?♫
Good.
♫The varied regrets we sing repeatedly♫
Actually, all of us
♫Have echoed for years♫
are walking on the same ground,
♫Hoping fate will amend♫
which is called destiny.
Life is like drifting fallen leaves,
♫Remember me, a humble♫
blown together by winds from all directions,
♫Blossom♫
gathering,
then separating.
I'm afraid.
I'm afraid that one day,
we will be blown apart
and crushed.
Don't be afraid.
How can I not be afraid?
I'm afraid of separation.
I'm afraid when I wake up from this dream,
there will only be a vast expanse of whiteness in the world.
No matter how long the dream is,
we will wake up.
We'll go back to reality,
but we'll remember the dream forever.
So,
don't be afraid.
Right.
You're the great demon dominating the two realms. With you protecting me,
I have nothing to be afraid of.
No wonder
you forced me to sign the contract of lifelong protection.
Yeah.
I need a strong fighter.
You
are Baize Goddess now.
Many great and little demons are watching you.
You must live.
They all rely
on you to protect them.
Why is it that every time I finish playing the wooden flute,
my heart aches
as if it's burning.
Okay.
Then let's live together.
What are you doing?
Since we agreed to live,
let's seal it.
I'll go find more livers.
No need.
Human livers can only slow down the spread of the poison.
I'm already seriously poisoned.
Don't bother.
Don't worry.
I will get the dragon scale to cure you.
He's still angry.
Zhuo,
stop being angry.
Next time, I'll act with you to fool Zhao Yuanzhou.
There's no next time.
I'm not good at pretending to quarrel,
either.
[One-Word Spell: act]
Zhao Yuanzhou.
Why is it not an option?
Oh.
Take the dragon scale.
You can use it to repair your Cloud Light Sword now.
There's no rush.
This is the only dragon scale.
Besides, we don't know how to repair the sword.
I think we'd better wait for Lord Bai Yan
to come back.
Right.
It's a matter of success and failure.
We can't be hasty.
For the time being,
the dragon scale...
Let me keep it.
You?
What?
Your expression
♫Leaving home, going far away from those mountains♫
is very insulting.
♫And that stream♫
Don't worry.
I'll keep it with me
♫The boy wiped away his tears and sang♫
and keep a close eye on it.
Even if Mount Tai collapses in front of me,
I won't even blink.
♫He carried his dreams with him♫
You're a Mountain God.
Is it appropriate for you
♫Jingling all the way♫
to say "Mount Tai collapses"?
♫Wind, rain, and light♫
Okay.
♫Wandering with me♫
I can trust Ying Lei
with the dragon scale.
This is about Jiu.
He'll put it ahead of himself.
♫Standing somewhere high and walking into the crowd♫
♫So what if I love the world more?♫
Okay.
But
♫The more ordinary it is, the longer it lasts♫
since Li Lun badly wants to stop us from repairing the sword,
♫The moon is nodding with me♫
he'll definitely come for the dragon scale.
♫A person who falls asleep in a simple way is the gentlest♫
Then I'll fight hard with him.
Seal.
To ensure its safety,
I set a restriction with my power.
No one can open the box.
Then nothing will go wrong.
Mr. Zhuo,
why are you here?
I'm worried.
I'm afraid Li Lun
will take away the dragon scale.
The dragon scale is safe.
I've been keeping an eye on it.
Let me take a look.
Sure.
You're not Mr. Zhuo.
You don't smell right.
Oh?
Then tell me
what Mr. Zhuo
smells like.
Cut the crap!
Ao Yin.
Hey!
[Ao Yin]
Stop!
Lord Bai Yan is back.
Let's take the dragon scale to him now
and ask him
how to repair the Cloud Light Sword.
Where is Ying Lei?
[Ao Yin]
It was Ao Yin again.
The dragon scale was taken away.
Looks like Ying Lei went after Ao Yin.
Let's go save him
and get the dragon scale back.
Mr. Zhuo,
what are you doing?
Is he
Ao Yin?
He is not Ao Yin.
He is Zhao Yuanzhou.
But he's hiding something from us.
Mr. Zhuo,
what do you mean?
Was the dragon scale really taken away by Ao Yin?
[Ao Yin]
The golden characters on the white wall
are solid evidence.
My lord,
I got the dragon scale.
I can't open it.
Give it to me.
I don't want the box.
Give me your hand.
My injury
is not serious.
You don't have much demonic power left.
Don't waste it on me.
I'm dying. My demonic power will be wasted
if I still keep it.
If I die,
I'll give you all my demonic power.
It's just a restriction.
Looks like Zhao Yuanzhou
has completely forgotten
he once taught me
all
his tricks.
My lord.
You are seriously poisoned.
Don't use your power lightly anymore.
Where is the dragon scale?